Are you
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): concerned that Israeli Defense Minister Katz said with respect to Lebanon that they were going to use the, quote, "Rafa model in Gaza"? Does that concern you? I have
Speaker 2: not. I'm not familiar with that
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): comment. You're responsible for ensuring that US arms transfers are consistent with the Trump administration's conventional arms transfer policy, right? Yes, sir. And that policy requires that you consider the risk that a proposed arms transfer may contribute to violations of international humanitarian law, right?
Speaker 3: Yes, sir.
Were
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): you involved in assessing that risk in connection with the administration's recent decision to invoke emergency powers to bypass congressional review
Speaker 4: and transfer over 20,000 bombs to the Netanyahu
Speaker 5 (lower-pitched voice): government? In response to the administration's emergency
Speaker 5 (lower-pitched voice): declaration I'm
Speaker 6: not asking you about I understand that but I think the context is important sir I know cuz I submitted a question for the record and you said you would comply with
Speaker 7 (lower-pitched voice): cat policy so now I'm asking you whether you were involved in reviewing the transfer of 20,000 bombs to the Netanyahu government with respect to compliance with the
cat policy any
Speaker 5 (lower-pitched voice): foreign military sale that we do
is
Speaker 5 (lower-pitched voice): would fall underneath the conventional arms transfer. Did you personally review-- I review hundreds of arms sales. I signed hundreds of them. The emergency declaration, again, it was consistent with the law.
Speaker 9: My comment-- But I'm not asking you about the-- I know, but I'm trying to address your concern. No, you're actually not. Yes, sir,
I am.
Are
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): you concerned that Israeli Defense Minister Katz said with respect to Lebanon that they were going to use the, quote, Rafa model in Gaza? Does that concern you? I'm not familiar
Speaker 2: with that comment. It's a
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): matter of public record. Could you
take a
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): look at it and get back to me? I would happily
look at
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): it. Let
Speaker 2: me know if that concerns you. Yes, sir. I'm happy to look at it. Thank you.